<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Art Gallery &#8211; cubatour</title>
	<atom:link href="https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/category/art-gallery/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:14:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tips for taking a longterm holiday plan this 2018</title>
		<link>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-longterm-holiday-plan-this-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-longterm-holiday-plan-this-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Art Gallery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wptravelenginedemo.com/travel-booking/?p=62</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Travel dates back to antiquity where wealthy Greeks and Romans would travel for leisure to their summer homes and villas in cities such as Pompeii and Baiae.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Travel dates back to antiquity where wealthy Greeks and Romans would travel for leisure to their summer homes and villas in cities such as Pompeii and Baiae.While early travel tended to be slower, more dangerous, and more dominated by trade and migration, cultural and technological advances over many years have tended to mean that travel has become easier and more accessible. Mankind has come a long way in transportation since Christopher Columbus sailed to the new world from Spain in 1492, an expedition which took over 10 weeks to arrive at the final destination; to the 21st century where aircraft allow travel from Spain to the United States overnight.</p>



<p>The origin of the word &#8220;travel&#8221; is most likely lost to history. The term &#8220;travel&#8221; may originate from the Old French word travail, which means &#8216;work&#8217;. According to the Merriam Webster dictionary, the first known use of the word travel was in the 14th century. It also states that the word comes from Middle English travailen, travelen (which means to torment, labor, strive, journey) and earlier from Old French travailler (which means to work strenuously, toil). In English we still occasionally use the words &#8220;travail&#8221;, which means struggle. According to Simon Winchester in his book The Best Travelers&#8217; Tales (2004), the words &#8220;travel&#8221; and &#8220;travail&#8221; both share an even more ancient root: a Roman instrument of torture called the tripalium (in Latin it means &#8220;three stakes&#8221;, as in to impale). This link may reflect the extreme difficulty of travel in ancient times. Today, travel may or may not be much easier depending upon the destination you choose (e.g. Mt. Everest, the Amazon rainforest), how you plan to get there (tour bus, cruise ship, or oxcart), and whether you decide to &#8220;rough it&#8221; (see extreme tourism and adventure travel). &#8220;There&#8217;s a big difference between simply being a tourist and being a true world traveler&#8221;, notes travel writer Michael Kasum. This is, however, a contested distinction as academic work on the cultures and sociology of travel has noted.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-longterm-holiday-plan-this-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips for taking a lognterm holidary plan this 2018</title>
		<link>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-lognterm-holidary-plan-this-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-lognterm-holidary-plan-this-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Art Gallery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wptravelenginedemo.com/travel-booking/?p=56</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nepal is a landlocked country in South Asia. It is located mainly in the Himalayas but also includes parts of the Indo-Gangetic Plain. With an estimated population of 26.4 million, &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Nepal is a landlocked country in South Asia. It is located mainly in the Himalayas but also includes parts of the Indo-Gangetic Plain. With an estimated population of 26.4 million, it is 48th largest country by population and 93rd largest country by area. It borders China in the north and India in the south, east, and west while Bangladesh is located within only 27 km (17 mi) of its southeastern tip and Bhutan is separated from it by the Indian state of Sikkim. Nepal has a diverse geography, including fertile plains, subalpine forested hills, and eight of the world&#8217;s ten tallest mountains, including Mount Everest, the highest point on Earth. Kathmandu is the nation&#8217;s capital and largest city. Nepal is a multiethnic nation with Nepali as the official language.</p>



<p>The name &#8220;Nepal&#8221; is first recorded in texts from the Vedic Age, the era in which Hinduism was founded, the predominant religion of the country. In the middle of the first millennium BCE, Gautama Buddha, the founder of Buddhism, was born in southern Nepal. Parts of northern Nepal were intertwined with the culture of Tibet. The centrally located Kathmandu Valley was the seat of the prosperous Newar confederacy known as Nepal Mandala. The Himalayan branch of the ancient Silk Road was dominated by the valley&#8217;s traders. The cosmopolitan region developed distinct traditional art and architecture. By the 18th century, the Gorkha Kingdom achieved the unification of Nepal. The Shah dynasty established the Kingdom of Nepal and later formed an alliance with the British Empire, under its Rana dynasty of premiers. The country was never colonised but served as a buffer state between Imperial China and colonial India.Parliamentary democracy was introduced in 1951, but was twice suspended by Nepalese monarchs, in 1960 and 2005. The Nepalese Civil War in the 1990s and early 2000s resulted in the proclamation of a secular republic in 2008, ending the world&#8217;s last Hindu monarchy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/tips-for-taking-a-lognterm-holidary-plan-this-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
