<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Street Walking &#8211; cubatour</title>
	<atom:link href="https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/category/street-walking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:11:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Readers&#8217; travel photography competition</title>
		<link>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/readers-travel-photography-competition/</link>
					<comments>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/readers-travel-photography-competition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mountaineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Street Walking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wptravelenginedemo.com/travel-booking/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In many societies there are important distinctions between holidays designated by governments and holidays designated by religious institutions. For example, in many predominantly Christian nations.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In many societies there are important distinctions between holidays designated by governments and holidays designated by religious institutions. For example, in many predominantly Christian nations, government-designed holidays may center on Christian holidays, though non-Christians may instead observe religious holidays associated with their faith. In some cases, a holiday may only be nominally observed. For example, many Jews in the Americas and Europe treat the relatively minor Jewish holiday of Hanukkah as a &#8220;working holiday&#8221;, changing very little of their daily routines for this day.</p>



<p>A holiday is a day set aside by custom or by law on which normal activities, especially business or work including school, are suspended or reduced. Generally, holidays are intended to allow individuals to celebrate or commemorate an event or tradition of cultural or religious significance. Holidays may be designated by governments, religious institutions, or other groups or organizations. The degree to which normal activities are reduced by a holiday may depend on local laws, customs, the type of job being held or personal choices.</p>



<p>The concept of holidays often originated in connection with religious observances. The intention of a holiday was typically to allow individuals to tend to religious duties associated with important dates on the calendar. In most modern societies, however, holidays serve as much of a recreational function as any other weekend days or activities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://alexmarke.github.io/cubatour/2022/03/15/readers-travel-photography-competition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
